nexusthemes.com 2018-09-16

# Nexus Themes

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.

## 1.1 Changes to this Privacy Policy

We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time by posting a new version online. You should check this page occasionally to review any changes. If we make any material changes we will notify you by posting the revised Privacy Policy on our Website. This helps you to always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances, if any, it is disclosed. Your continued use of the Website, our Services, and/or continued provision of Personal Information to us will be subject to the terms of the then-current Privacy Policy.

## 1.2 Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our treatment of the information you provide us, please write to us by email at [info@nexusthemes.com](mailto:info@nexustemes.com)

## 2.1 Usage of Our Services

Our customers use our Services to build websites that people can visit to learn more about their business or their client's businesses. Nexus Themes does not control the content of these webpages or the types of information that our customers may choose to collect or manage using our Services. That information belongs to them and is used, disclosed and protected by them according to their privacy policies and is not subject to this Privacy Policy. Nexus Themes processes our customers' information as they direct and in accordance with our agreements with our customers, and we store it on our service providers' servers, but we do not have control over its collection or management. Our agreements with our customers prohibit us from using that information, except as necessary to provide and improve the Services, as permitted by this Privacy Policy, and as required by law. We have no direct relationship with individuals who provide Personal Information to our customers. Nexus Themes acknowledges that you have the right to access your Personal Information. Our customers control and are responsible for correcting, deleting or updating information they have collected from you using our Services. If requested to remove data we will respond within a reasonable timeframe. We may work with our customers to help them provide notice to their visitors about their data collection, processing and usage. Our agreements with our customers prohibit them from using the our Services to collect, manage, or process Sensitive Information. We are not responsible for our customers' use of information they collect on the our Services. 

Nexus Themes collects information under the direction of its customers, and has no direct relationship with the individuals whose Personal Information it processes. If you are a customer of one of our customers and would no longer like to be contacted by one of our customer that use any of our Services, please contact the customer that you interact with directly. We may transfer Personal Information to companies that help us provide our service. Transfers to subsequent third parties are covered by the service agreements with our customers.

## 2.2 Information We Collect and Why We Collect It

In the course of providing our services, we collect or receive your personal information in a few different ways. We have created an extensive "[DPA Exhibit](https://nexusthemes.com/dpa-exhibit-1017/)" overview where you can view all of the processes which involve the storage and processing of personal data.

## 2.3 Compliance with this Privacy Policy

We use the information we collect only in compliance with this Privacy Policy. Customers who use our Services are obligated through our agreements with them to comply with this Privacy Policy.

## 2.4 Who We Share Your Data With

Please consult our [DPA Exhibit](https://nexusthemes.com/dpa-exhibit-1017/) to learn more about if we share your data with third parties.

## 3.1 Use of Personal Information

In addition to the uses identified elsewhere in this Privacy Policy, we may use your Personal Information to: (a) improve your browsing experience by personalizing the Website and to improve our Services; (b) send information to you which we think may be of interest to you by email, or other means; and (c) send you marketing communications relating to our business or the businesses of carefully-selected third parties which we think may be of interest to you -- but this information will not be used to identify any individual user. In addition, we may engage trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, or provide customer support. Such third parties are prohibited from using your Personal Information except for these purposes, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information. If you do not want us to share your personal information with these companies, contact us at [info@nexusthemes.com](mailto:info@nexustemes.com).

## 3.2 Security of Your Personal Information

The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and after it is received. For more information please consult the [DPA Exhibit page](https://nexusthemes.com/dpa-exhibit-1017/).

## 3.3 Retention of Personal Information

Both because of legal obligations (tax returns) and to streamline our services we retain personal information for longer periods of time. For more information please consult the [DPA Exhibit page](https://nexusthemes.com/dpa-exhibit-1017/).

## 3.4 Compelled Disclosure

We reserve the right to use or disclose your Personal Information if required by law or if we reasonably believe that use or disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or comply with a law, court order, or legal process.

## 3.5 Data Breach Procedure

We adhere to the Data Breach Procedure as stipulated by the GDPR. Meaning in case of a data breach as defined by the GDPR we will report our national GDPR enforcer within 72 hours after the breach has been found. After the proper research has been done about the breach and if necessary we will inform the user concerns.

## 4.1 Cookies

We use cookies or similar technologies to analyze trends, administer the website, track users’ movements around the website, and to gather demographic information about our website visitors. We use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web server. Cookies are not used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a Web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize pages in a Trial Environment we provide, a cookie helps us to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. When you return to the same Environment, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the customized features. 

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of our Websites. We keeps track of the pages you visit, in order to determine what portion of our Site is the most popular or most used. This data is used to optimize our Service to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area. 

For more information please consult the [DPA Exhibit page](https://nexusthemes.com/dpa-exhibit-1017/).

## 4.2 Log Files

We may collect information that can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, internet service provider (ISP), the files viewed on our site (e.g., HTML pages, graphics, etc.), operating system, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used by Nexus Themes for the operation of the our Services, to maintain quality of the Service, remove possible unwanted users from harming our online ecosystem and to provide general statistics regarding use of the our Website. For more information please consult the [DPA Exhibit page](https://nexusthemes.com/dpa-exhibit-1017/).

## 4.3 Advertising

We partner with a third party ad network to manage our advertising on other sites. Our ad network partner uses cookies and Web beacons to collect non-personal information about your activities on this website to provide you targeted advertising based upon your interests. For more information please consult the [DPA Exhibit page](https://nexusthemes.com/dpa-exhibit-1017/).

## 5.1 Reviewing, Correcting and Removing Your Personal Information

The GDPR offers people a number of rights concerning their personal information. We adhere to all of these with respect to data deletion, data transparency, data portability and data modification. When we are legally obliged to retain certain personal information, this obligation trumps the user rights. For instance, a person cannot demand us to delete financial transactions, because this would imply a breach of our legal accounting standards. If you have any questions related to your rights concerning personal information and the way we handle it, feel free to send an email to [info@nexusthemes.com](mailto:info@nexustemes.com)

## 6.1 Third Party Data Processing Agreements (DPA)

We make extensive use of professional third party suppliers of services (processors) which are a core part of our operations. Services which fall in this category is cloud hosting, email services, WordPress, payment providing and the like. To ensure your personal information is being dealt with in a way befitting the GDPR we've researched the parties in question and have obtained the relevant DPA's (Data Processing Agreements). For more information please consult the [DPA Exhibit page](https://nexusthemes.com/dpa-exhibit-1017/).
